[
  {
    "question": "What is 39 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "327",
      "324",
      "320",
      "321"
    ],
    "answer": "324"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 22 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "-732",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-732"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 332?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "13",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "-122",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-122"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 993?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "24",
      "22",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "-188",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-188"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 \u00f7 9?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "6",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 10 in 969?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "2",
      "4",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 2?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "14",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 31 in 992?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-2",
      "-3",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 35?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "28",
      "29",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 11?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "27",
      "22",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "-260"
    ],
    "answer": "-260"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 21?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "41",
      "43",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 50?",
    "options": [
      "98",
      "95",
      "100",
      "101"
    ],
    "answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-837",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-837"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 6?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-549",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-549"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 7?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 11?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "5",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 5?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "10",
      "15",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 602?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "12",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 \u00f7 7?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "1",
      "0",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 29?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "38",
      "37",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 \u00f7 10?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-1",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 3?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "41",
      "36",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 932?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "17",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 42 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "742",
      "743",
      "739",
      "740"
    ],
    "answer": "743"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 37?",
    "options": [
      "77",
      "79",
      "78",
      "74"
    ],
    "answer": "74"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 32?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "39",
      "46",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 7?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 36?",
    "options": [
      "67",
      "72",
      "70",
      "74"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 31?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "23",
      "21",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "422",
      "427",
      "425",
      "424"
    ],
    "answer": "422"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 39?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "47",
      "50",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 15?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "5",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 43?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "90",
      "87",
      "82"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "-237",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-237"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "3",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 467?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "16",
      "17",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 40 in 756?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "0",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 20?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "41",
      "44",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 \u00f7 10?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "7",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 9?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "17",
      "14",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 38?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "16",
      "20",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 34 \u00f7 8?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "7",
      "8",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 45 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "930",
      "929",
      "934",
      "933"
    ],
    "answer": "930"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 5?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "13",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-363",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-363"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-393",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-393"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 25?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "15",
      "20",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 32 in 878?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 156?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 \u00f7 10?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-1",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 25 in 551?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 26 in 392?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "-4",
      "0",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 130?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "9",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "133",
      "140",
      "139",
      "136"
    ],
    "answer": "136"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 41?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "55",
      "47",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 31?",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "62",
      "57",
      "65"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "-544",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-544"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 12 in 179?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "0",
      "2",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 34?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "19",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 798?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "23",
      "29",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 7?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "4",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 2?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 38?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "31",
      "33",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 6?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "7",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "129",
      "125",
      "130",
      "123"
    ],
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 31?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "46",
      "41",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 611?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "3",
      "11",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 45 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-533",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-533"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 45 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "410",
      "411",
      "406",
      "416"
    ],
    "answer": "411"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 45?",
    "options": [
      "87",
      "95",
      "90",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 494?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "17",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 19?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "35",
      "43",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 769?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "26",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 \u00f7 11?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "-1",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 9?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "18",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 44?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "22",
      "26",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 653?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "10",
      "12",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 9?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 23?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "15",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 22?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 21?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "11",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "488",
      "485",
      "483",
      "487"
    ],
    "answer": "488"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 1 in 453?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-2",
      "5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 886?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "17",
      "21",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 + 7?",
    "options": [
      "904",
      "905",
      "908",
      "907"
    ],
    "answer": "907"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 32 + 7?",
    "options": [
      "710",
      "715",
      "711",
      "706"
    ],
    "answer": "711"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 180?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "9",
      "4",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 25?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "38",
      "35",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "-1",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 9?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "16",
      "13",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "261",
      "268",
      "269",
      "264"
    ],
    "answer": "264"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 5?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 29 in 353?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "4",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "1",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "-250"
    ],
    "answer": "-250"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 34 in 987?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 29?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "39",
      "34",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 3?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "8",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "13",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 8?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "4",
      "-1",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 40?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "25",
      "20",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "779",
      "771",
      "775",
      "776"
    ],
    "answer": "775"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 295?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "16",
      "15",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 13?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "26",
      "23",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 31?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "26",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 45 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "976",
      "974",
      "969",
      "973"
    ],
    "answer": "973"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 26 in 279?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "-5",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 558?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "18",
      "14",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 15?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "30",
      "32",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 21?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "12",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 30 in 996?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "0",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 42?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "33",
      "32",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 35?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "29",
      "25",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 243?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "9",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 \u00d7 10?",
    "options": [
      "501",
      "503",
      "500",
      "498"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 8?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 788?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "25",
      "23",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "335",
      "336",
      "332",
      "333"
    ],
    "answer": "336"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 38 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-936",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-936"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 45?",
    "options": [
      "92",
      "89",
      "90",
      "86"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 718?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "14",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "218",
      "221",
      "222",
      "219"
    ],
    "answer": "222"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 16?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "29",
      "30",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 38 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-949",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-949"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 18?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "40",
      "31",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 25?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "9",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "35",
      "37",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "405",
      "409",
      "407",
      "400"
    ],
    "answer": "405"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "106",
      "109",
      "105",
      "108"
    ],
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 39?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "20",
      "22",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 \u00f7 6?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "1",
      "5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 43?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "52",
      "57",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "53"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 21?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "10",
      "13",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 9?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "22",
      "21",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-948",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-948"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "14",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 \u00f7 12?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-4",
      "0",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 \u00f7 12?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 34 in 178?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "0",
      "-5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 44?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "54",
      "53",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 13?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "-2",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 23 in 926?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "2",
      "0",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-264",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-264"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "371",
      "368",
      "363",
      "365"
    ],
    "answer": "368"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "19",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 805?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "13",
      "11",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-609",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-609"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 34?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "41",
      "46",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "190",
      "191",
      "192",
      "189"
    ],
    "answer": "192"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 33 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "-488",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-488"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 590?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "19",
      "9",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 5 in 524?",
    "options": [
      "505",
      "500",
      "495",
      "501"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 43?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "16",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 15?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "24",
      "23",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 34?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "20",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "90",
      "95",
      "88",
      "92"
    ],
    "answer": "92"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "793",
      "798",
      "802",
      "799"
    ],
    "answer": "798"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 39?",
    "options": [
      "83",
      "81",
      "82",
      "78"
    ],
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 938?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "25",
      "19",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 13?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "23",
      "31",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 25?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "9",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 27?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "15",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "129",
      "120",
      "125",
      "127"
    ],
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 15 in 105?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "196",
      "197",
      "198",
      "194"
    ],
    "answer": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 784?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "18",
      "19",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 24?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "96",
      "97",
      "93",
      "92"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "232",
      "237",
      "229",
      "235"
    ],
    "answer": "232"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "702",
      "703",
      "708",
      "705"
    ],
    "answer": "705"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 38 in 108?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "5",
      "4",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 40?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "48",
      "50",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 39 in 747?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "-702",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-702"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 11 in 947?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "0",
      "2",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 35?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 118?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "13",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 28?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "-229"
    ],
    "answer": "-229"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "-643"
    ],
    "answer": "-643"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 29?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "16",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 25?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "51",
      "46",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 18?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "40",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 9?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "24",
      "22",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 20?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 489?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "25",
      "21",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 366?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "15",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 7 in 889?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 36?",
    "options": [
      "75",
      "73",
      "72",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-420"
    ],
    "answer": "-420"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 435?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 38?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "74",
      "72",
      "77"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 37 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "-365"
    ],
    "answer": "-365"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 21?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "30",
      "26",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "-168"
    ],
    "answer": "-168"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-200"
    ],
    "answer": "-200"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 38?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "19",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 19 in 134?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "0",
      "5",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 40?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "18",
      "20",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 + 10?",
    "options": [
      "565",
      "567",
      "570",
      "568"
    ],
    "answer": "568"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 2?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "5",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "-464",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-464"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "299",
      "301",
      "300",
      "302"
    ],
    "answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 25?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "16",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 5?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "4",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 34 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "206",
      "208",
      "201",
      "204"
    ],
    "answer": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 20?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "39",
      "40",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 35?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "13",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "54",
      "58",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "145",
      "142",
      "141",
      "143"
    ],
    "answer": "143"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 + 5?",
    "options": [
      "878",
      "880",
      "875",
      "877"
    ],
    "answer": "877"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "482",
      "480",
      "477",
      "479"
    ],
    "answer": "479"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 45 in 560?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "5",
      "-4",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 6?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 46?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "20",
      "19",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 + 5?",
    "options": [
      "596",
      "594",
      "601",
      "600"
    ],
    "answer": "596"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 29?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "15",
      "17",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 35?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "47",
      "45",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 8?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "6",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 36 in 624?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "-720",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-720"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 275?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "19",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 500?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 111?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 5 in 544?",
    "options": [
      "500",
      "496",
      "497",
      "501"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 581?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "16",
      "14",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "-695"
    ],
    "answer": "-695"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "86",
      "85",
      "89"
    ],
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 36 in 169?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "2",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "17",
      "12",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 8?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "7",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "947",
      "944",
      "943",
      "938"
    ],
    "answer": "943"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 376?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "16",
      "20",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 18?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "13",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "839",
      "833",
      "836",
      "835"
    ],
    "answer": "836"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 26 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "-930",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-930"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 9?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-1",
      "-4",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "214",
      "215",
      "216",
      "219"
    ],
    "answer": "215"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 739?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "20",
      "24",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 460?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "13",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "521",
      "520",
      "524",
      "526"
    ],
    "answer": "524"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 322?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "11",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 34 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "903",
      "907",
      "911",
      "910"
    ],
    "answer": "907"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 44 in 669?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "4",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 11?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "18",
      "26",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 40?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "45",
      "50",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "608",
      "607",
      "613",
      "610"
    ],
    "answer": "610"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 2 in 829?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "24",
      "22",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "29",
      "28",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "960",
      "958",
      "956",
      "959"
    ],
    "answer": "960"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 43?",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "86",
      "87",
      "89"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 47?",
    "options": [
      "99",
      "93",
      "94",
      "95"
    ],
    "answer": "94"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "561",
      "566",
      "567",
      "565"
    ],
    "answer": "565"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "341",
      "342",
      "338",
      "343"
    ],
    "answer": "341"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "5",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 16?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "6",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 33?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "43",
      "47",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "7",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 5?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "7",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 23?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 7?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "18",
      "21",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 23?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "46",
      "48",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-421",
      "Square",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-421"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 33?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "21",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 5 in 976?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "-4",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "20",
      "26",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "491",
      "492",
      "494",
      "493"
    ],
    "answer": "492"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 29?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "39",
      "36",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "-242",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-242"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 24?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "19",
      "17",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 32 in 896?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-5",
      "0",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 32?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "42",
      "43",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 27?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "54",
      "51",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 33?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "26",
      "21",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 12?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 26 in 556?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "4",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 50 in 573?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "-3",
      "-1",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 38 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "702",
      "692",
      "697",
      "693"
    ],
    "answer": "697"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 2?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "17",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "623",
      "627",
      "622",
      "624"
    ],
    "answer": "622"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "344",
      "348",
      "346",
      "349"
    ],
    "answer": "344"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 25?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "12",
      "15",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 \u00f7 7?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "8",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "324",
      "329",
      "322",
      "320"
    ],
    "answer": "324"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 36?",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "72",
      "67",
      "68"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 32?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "21",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 30 in 924?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "5",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 355?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "17",
      "18",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 21 in 744?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "0",
      "-2",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 13?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "9",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 11?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "-2",
      "0",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 49 in 502?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "2",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-725",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-725"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 239?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "19",
      "14",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "537",
      "532",
      "538",
      "541"
    ],
    "answer": "537"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 44?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "24",
      "19",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 1?",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "47",
      "50",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 994?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "18",
      "19",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 30?",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "61",
      "56",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 26 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-598",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-598"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 6?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "-3",
      "0",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 1?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "29",
      "27",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 10?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 12?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "25",
      "19",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 37?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "18",
      "20",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 38 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-199",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-199"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 49?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "42",
      "37",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 633?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "8",
      "12",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 35?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "25",
      "21",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 43 in 252?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-4",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 859?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "23",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 17?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "8",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 3?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "-3",
      "1",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-102",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-102"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 38?",
    "options": [
      "81",
      "78",
      "76",
      "74"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "-654",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-654"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "35",
      "37",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 9?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "3",
      "4",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 26?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "10",
      "11",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 44?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "53",
      "54",
      "55"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 19?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "41",
      "33",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 26?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "11",
      "13",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 17?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "12",
      "4",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "70",
      "63",
      "66"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 14?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "28",
      "23",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 536?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "14",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 42?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "51",
      "52",
      "56"
    ],
    "answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-94"
    ],
    "answer": "-94"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 41?",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "80",
      "87",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "82"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 44?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "18",
      "22",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "39",
      "36",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 11 in 649?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 5?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "14",
      "20",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 18?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "8",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 29 in 640?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "-3",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 39?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "32",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 30?",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "59",
      "58",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 1?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "37",
      "33",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 14?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "26",
      "25",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 10?",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "57",
      "63",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "198",
      "208",
      "201",
      "203"
    ],
    "answer": "203"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "140",
      "143",
      "144",
      "146"
    ],
    "answer": "143"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-950",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-950"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 21 \u00f7 10?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "6",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "15",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 42 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "-580",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-580"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 587?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "20",
      "21",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 \u00f7 12?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "5",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 30?",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "59",
      "60",
      "62"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 13?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 8?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "7",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 6?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "5",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-581"
    ],
    "answer": "-581"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 35 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "-83",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-83"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 47?",
    "options": [
      "95",
      "93",
      "92",
      "94"
    ],
    "answer": "94"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "8",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 898?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "25",
      "29",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 26 in 137?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "1",
      "0",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 18 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "605",
      "607",
      "613",
      "608"
    ],
    "answer": "608"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-201",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-201"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 7?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "4",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 31 in 435?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "0",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 19 in 426?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "-1",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "372",
      "377",
      "378",
      "375"
    ],
    "answer": "377"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 17 in 190?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "3",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 9?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-1",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 4?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 7?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "22",
      "18",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 32 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "883",
      "884",
      "881",
      "879"
    ],
    "answer": "884"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 47?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "34",
      "37",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "-293",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-293"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 5?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "13",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "572",
      "570",
      "568",
      "567"
    ],
    "answer": "572"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 10 in 280?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "3",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 897?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "21",
      "28",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 275?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 34 in 543?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "2",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 33?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "11",
      "16",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 \u00f7 3?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "10",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "-154"
    ],
    "answer": "-154"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 22 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-834",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-834"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 less than 37?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "28",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 38?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "80",
      "78",
      "72"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 24 in 760?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "-5",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 34?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "49",
      "44",
      "47"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 1?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "23",
      "25",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "609",
      "606",
      "605",
      "603"
    ],
    "answer": "605"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "-367",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-367"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 30?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "18",
      "15",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of digits of 317?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number is 10 more than 10?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "20",
      "19",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of 12 in 709?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "0",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is half of 36?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "17",
      "23",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  }
]